(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-24T22:12:49.286854",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.7-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Grimoire 4 Ever ～四人で綴られ、永遠に残る魔導書～
Grimoire 4 Ever ~A Grimoire Woven by Four, Remaining Forever~
桃鈴ねね
Momosuzu Nene
尾丸ポルカ
Omaru Polka
雪花ラミィ
Yukihana Lamy
獅白ぼたん
Shishiro Botan
Grimoire 4 Ever ～四人で綴られ、永遠に残る魔導書～
Grimoire 4 Ever ~A Grimoire Woven by Four, Remaining Forever~
Twinkle 4 You (Grimoire Remix)
君に届け 星のメロディー
Reach for you, melody of the stars
想いをギュッとギュッと詰め込んで
Packing my feelings tight, so tight
君と奏でる このハーモニー
This harmony I play together with you
これからも ずっと続いてく
Will continue on forever from now on
ねぇねぇ もっと近くにおいでよ
Hey, hey, come closer to me
回り始めた世界で 踊らない？ 終わらない
In this world that's started to spin, won't you dance? It won't end!
わくわく 魔法かけたら
Once I cast an exciting spell
ドキドキはSyncして ほら Party Time 止まらない
Our heartbeats sync up, look, this Party Time won't stop!
Twinkle Twinkle Little Stars
願いを込めて
Making a wish
Twinkle Twinkle
夜空で
In the night sky,
歌いましょう
let's sing together!
君に響け 星のメロディー
Resonate to you, melody of the stars
新しい星座を描いて
Drawing new constellations
君と繋がっている この空に
In this sky where I'm connected with you,
宝石を散りばめよう
let's scatter jewels all around
君に届け 星のメロディー
Reach for you, melody of the stars
想いをギュッとギュッと詰め込んで
Packing my feelings tight, so tight
君と奏でる このハーモニー
This harmony I play together with you
これからも ずっと続いてく
Will continue on forever from now on
Clap Clap ほら 一緒に鳴らそう
Clap, clap, come on, let's clap together!
この瞬間をキャッチして 忘れない Starry Night
Catching this moment on this unforgettable Starry Night
キラキラ 魔法解けても
Sparkling bright, even if the magic wears off
胸にしまったトキメキは 消えない 止まらない
The excitement locked in my heart won't fade or stop!
Twinkle Twinkle Little Stars
願いを込めて
Making a wish
Twinkle Twinkle
夜空で
In the night sky,
踊りましょう
let's dance!
Twinkle 4 You
Twinkle for you
君と残す 星のメモリー
A starry memory left behind with you
思い出ギュッとギュッと詰め込んで
Packing all our memories tight, so tight
君と会えた
Getting to meet you,
この素敵な奇跡と...
this wonderful miracle and...
奇跡と夢を
The miracle and dream...
また叶えよう
let's make them come true again.
君に響け 星のメロディー
Echo to you, melody of the stars,
新しい星座を描いて
drawing a new constellation.
君と繋がっているこの宇宙に
In this sky connecting me with you,
宝石を散りばめよう
let's scatter jewels across it.
君に届け 星のメロディー
Reach to you, melody of the stars,
想いをギュッとギュッと詰め込んで
tightly, tightly packing our feelings inside.
君と奏でるこのハーモニー
This harmony played with you,
これからもずっと続いてく
will keep on continuing forever.
La la la la la la la...
イエーイ！
Yeah!
始まりましたー！
It's started!
というわけで皆さん、ねぽらぼ4周年記念ライブ「Grimoire FOREVER」へお越しいただきありがとうございます！
And so everyone, thank you so much for coming to NePoLaBo's 4th Anniversary Live, "Grimoire FOREVER"!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
はい、我らがねぽらぼでーす！
Yes, we are NePoLaBo!
イエーイ！
Yeah!
というわけで簡単な一言自己紹介、ねねからどうぞ！
So, let's do quick one-liner introductions. Nene, go ahead!
はい！ホロライブ5期生、オレンジの魔法、
Yes! Hololive 5th Gen, orange magic,
ピンクの桃もじり、
pink play on "momo",
みんなのエナジードリンク、桃鈴ねねでーす！
everyone's energy drink, I'm Momosuzu Nene!
ありがとうございます！イエーイ！
Thank you so much! Yay!
はい、ポルカです！ポルカおるかー？おるよー！
Yes, I'm Polka! Is Polka here? Here I am!
あか、赤色の魔法で合ってんのか？
Red... red-colored magic, is that right?
はい、ポルカです！よろしくお願いします！
Yes, I'm Polka! Nice to meet you!
よろしくお願いしまーす！はい次ラミィ！
Nice to meet you! Next up, Lamy!
はい！ホロライブの顔が肝臓、雪花ラミィです！青色の魔法でーす！
Yes! Hololive's face is my liver, I'm Yukihana Lamy! Blue magic!
青は肝臓の魔法？
Blue is liver magic?
よろしくお願いしまーす！
Nice to meet you!
はい、じゃあねぽらぼの「ぼ」、黒魔道士、獅白ぼたんです！
Yes, I'm the "Bo" of NePoLaBo, the black mage, Shishiro Botan!
おー！強そう！
Ooh! Sounds strong!
黒魔道士、かっこいい！／この世の全てを滅ぼしに…
Black mage, so cool! / I came to destroy everything in this world...
えー、今回のですね、配信のハッシュタグはこちらー！
Um, the hashtag for today's stream is right here!
ばばーん！
Ta-da!
ハッシュタグ「#ねぽらぼ4周年3Dライブ」こちらでお願いします！
Hashtag "#Nepolabo4thAnniversary3DLive", please post with this!
お願いしまーす！
Please do!
皆さんたくさんポストしてください！ラミィたちもチェックしまーす！
Everyone, please post a lot! We'll be checking them too!
後で見ましょう！
Let's check them later!
目指せトレンド1位！／目指せ！
Aim for trending number 1! / Let's aim for it!
そして、いよいよ周年ライブ始まりましたけど、どうですか皆さん！
And so, our anniversary live has finally begun, how are you all doing?
いや、ワクワク、ドキドキ…／緊張も…
We're so excited, nervous... / A bit tense too...
ねねちゃん、今回のライブコンセプトを説明していただけますか？
Nene-chan, could you explain the concept for today's live?
あ、そうだね！コンセプトはね、はい！
Ah, right! The concept is, yes!
「8月の魔法」！
"August Magic"!
キャッチコピーは「4人で綴られ永遠に残る魔道書」！
The tagline is "A grimoire written by the four of us that will remain forever"!
魔法少女をイメージとした帽子とステッキ！
Hats and wands themed after magical girls!
素敵だね！
How wonderful!
こちらを特別に作っていただきました！
These were specially made for us!
はい！イエーイ！
Yes! Yay!
そしてですね、そのコンセプトにあったステージも作っていただきました！
And we also had a stage created to match this concept!
うわー！すごい！壮大！
Whoa! Incredible! So grand!
これウチら浮いてる、宇宙だね！
We're floating here, in space!
この星空に囲まれたステージで今日はライブをするんだね！
We get to perform our live today on a stage surrounded by the starry sky!
そうですよ！すごい！
That's right! Amazing!
あ、見てこれ！専用の足元に…魔法陣！
Ah, look at this! Under our feet... magic circles!
ねねさん、ねねさんあっちやん！
Nene-san, yours is over there!
あれ、どこだ？あ、後ろ？こっちこっち、ここか！
Huh, where? Ah, behind? This way, this way, here!
専用魔法陣もあるのすごい！
It's so cool that we have our own custom magic circles!
これライブでいっぱい見せていきたいね！
We want to show this off a lot during the live!
まあそんな中でね、1曲目からみんなで魔法とかもかけまくっちゃったわけですけども。
Well, with all that, we've already been casting tons of magic since the very first song.
どうでしたか？魔法。
How was it? The magic.
魔法かけてた！まず1曲目『Twinkle 4 You』をGrimoire Remixということで、新しく…
We cast magic! First, our 1st song "Twinkle 4 You" was the Grimoire Remix, a new...
リミックスしていただきました！ちょっと違ったでしょ、いつもと！
...remix made for us! It was a bit different from usual, right?
ちょっと違ったよね、いつもと。／違ったー！
It was a bit different from usual. / It was!
ちょっとタイミング難しいとことかあるんだよね。
There are parts where the timing gets tricky, right?
そうそうそう！何回も練習したね！あそこ難しかったけど…
Exactly! We practiced so many times! That part was tough...
まあ何とか今日も頑張りましたね、皆さん！／頑張りましたー！
Well, we managed to pull it off today, everyone! / We did!
ね、そこで魔道書に魔法で映像投影したり、あと歌詞の上の方に出したりしてもらいました。
Right, and we had visuals projected onto the grimoire with magic, and lyrics displayed up above.
そうね！この空間に…
Right! In this space...
ね、魔法に頑張っていただきました。
Yeah, the magic worked hard for us.
いや、魔法すごいな、やっぱり。流れ星とかもね、降らしたからね、魔法で。
Man, magic really is amazing. We even made shooting stars fall with magic.
え、前は魔法とかやってたけど、どうなの？今はできるんですか？
Well, we used magic before, but what about now? Can we still do it?
まあ見逃した人もいるか。実はもう今日のために魔法ステッキも用意してもらったってことで、魔法が使えるんですわ！
Well, some people might have missed it. We actually had magic wands prepared for today, so we can use magic!
そう、使えるんですわ、魔法が！
Yes, we can use magic!
ちょっとポルカね、やってみよう…
Let Polka try doing it...
ほら、やってやって！
Come on, do it, do it!
じゃあハートを出します！
Well then, I'll make hearts appear!
う〜ん…すいすいすいすい…ぽ〜ん！
Mmm... sui sui sui sui... poon!
そういう感じなんだ！可愛いけど
So that's how it works! It's cute, though.
可愛い！ハート飛んだね！これうち等も出せんの？
Cute! Hearts flew out! Can we do it too?
え、やってみる？あ、じゃあししろ行ってみる？
Want to try? Oh, shall Shishiro give it a go?
挙手制。う〜〜〜…はぁーーー！
By show of hands. Mmm... Haaah!
出し方！そういう感じなんだｗ
What a way to cast it! So that's how it is, haha.
出た！可愛い！可愛いけど…
It came out! Cute! Cute, but...
可愛いけどｗ ラミィもやってよ
Cute, but... haha! Lamy, you try too!
あ、いいよ〜！
Ah, okay~!
はい！らぶ・ちゅっ！…ん〜〜まっ！
Here goes! Love chu! ...Mmm-wah!
うわ可愛い！飛んだ！
Whoa, cute! It flew!
あ〜〜〜！
Aaaah~!
え、じゃあねねちゃんも…
Eh, then Nene-chan will too...
え〜…らぶ・ちゅっ！う〜ん、桃汁〜！
Umm... Love chu! Mmm, peach juice~!
うわっ！何個出んの！？すごい！
Whoa! How many are coming out?! Amazing!
魔法が分かんなくなってきたよ、これじゃｗ
I'm losing track of what magic is at this point, haha.
え、面白いなぁ。ね、すごい
Heh, this is fun. Yeah, amazing.
でもせっかくだからね、みんなの魔法をもっと見せてほしいなと思うんですけど…
But since we're here, I'd like everyone to show us more magic...
おっ？なんですかねねさん。まずは手始めにね…
Oh? What is it, Nene-san? First, to start off...
ねねが、この空間をちょっとだけ…
Nene will change this space...
変えたいと思います！みんな何が変わるかよく見ててね！
just a little bit! Everyone, watch closely to see what changes!
そんな分かんないの？分かんないとこある？
Is it that hard to notice? Is there something subtle?
う〜〜〜ん…えいっ！
Uuuun... Ei!
え？何？うわぁ！でっか！
Eh? What? Whoa! Huge!
本が大きくなって迫ってきた！迫ってきた！
The book grew huge and came closer! It's looming over us!
迫ってきた迫ってきた！びっくりした〜
It approached, it approached! That startled me~
いいでしょ！魔導書が大きくなった！すごい！大迫力！
Pretty cool, right? The grimoire got huge! Amazing! Such impact!
じゃあこの魔導書をちょっと使ってさ、ちょっと私たちの召喚魔法を見せようじゃないですか！
Then let's use this grimoire and show off our summoning magic!
ししろんそんなものが使えるのか。いや、これはね、みんなのパワーが要ります
Shishiron, you can use something like that? No, this requires everyone's power.
なるほど！頑張ろう！見ててね〜、応援してね〜
I see! Let's do our best! Watch us~ cheer for us~
じゃあ、行きますよ〜！はーい！せーの！
Alright, here we go~! Yes! Ready, set...
うーーーーーー…えーーーーい！
Uuuuuuu... Eeeeeei!
おお〜！かっこいい！すげえ！
Ooh! Cool! Amazing!
何が出てくる…？うわあああ！
What's coming out...? Uwaaaah!
出たー！降りてきてるー！
They're here! They're coming down!
ありがとう〜！ねっ子！雪民！SSRB！座員ちゃんじゃないか！
Thank you~! Nekko! Yukimin! SSRB! And Zain-chan!
召喚できました！よかった〜！召喚成功！
We summoned them! Thank goodness! Summoning success!
やったね〜！じゃあ一緒にね、これでみんなも集合したことだし…見守っていてくれるか？
We did it~! So together, now that everyone is gathered here... will you watch over us?
ありがとう〜！見守っててね〜。頑張るよ〜
Thank you~! Watch over us~ We'll do our best~
よーし！じゃあそろそろ次の曲いっちゃいましょうか！はーい！
Alright! Then shall we move on to the next song soon? Yes!
でもさっきので結構MP使ったけど大丈夫そう？マジックポイント
Wait, we used quite a bit of MP just now, are you guys okay? Magic points.
まだまだ！行けますよ！いけるよ〜！
Not yet, not yet! We can keep going! We're good to go~!
オッケー！じゃあこの後も楽しんでいってください！それじゃ次の…次の曲、レッツゴー！
Okay! Then please continue to enjoy the rest of the show! And so the next... next song, let's go!
レッツゴー！楽しんでね〜！
Let's go! Enjoy~!
悪戯に君をずっと見ていたわけじゃない
It's not like I was playfully staring at you the whole time.
僕の考えを当ててごらんよ
Try guessing what I'm thinking.
些細な仕草 視線 瞬き
A subtle gesture, a glance, a blink—
君はもう掌に
you're already in the palm of my hand.
剥き出しのtrap なんてかかるわけないわ
There's no way I'd fall for such an obvious trap.
甘い言葉にも惑わされない
Sweet words won't deceive me either.
心の奥の奥の奥まで
Deep, deep, deep down in your heart,
見透かしちゃうよ
I can see right through you.
Looking, thinking, touching, feeling, why you know?
Looking, thinking, touching, feeling, I know it
Looking, thinking, touching, feeling, understand?
Meaning, meaning of love, are you ready?
自覚ないでしょうね 思い通りに
You probably don't even realize it—
君は動かされている事!
that you're being moved just as intended!
単純じゃないの 駆け引きのhintを
It's not so simple; every hint in this bargaining,
全て見落とさないで
don't overlook a single one.
Meaning of love, meaning of love 加速してく
Meaning of love, meaning of love Quickening now,
Meaning of love, meaning of love 二人の鼓動
Meaning of love, meaning of love our two heartbeats.
Meaning of love, meaning of love 心理戦は 次のstageへ
Meaning of love, meaning of love This psychological game moves to the next stage.
虚ろなその目に 私はどう映るの
In those vacant eyes, how do I appear to you?
とても煌びやかで まるでcinderella
So dazzling, just like Cinderella.
突き刺さる視線 ズキンと感じて
Feeling your piercing gaze strike right through,
君に余裕見せつけて
I'll show off my composure to you.
あからさま過ぎて お腹が捩れるよ
You're so obvious it makes my sides split.
既に君はもう出来上がってる
You're already completely under my spell.
頭で次の次の次まで
In your head, to the next, and next, and next move,
見通さなくちゃ
you have to see right through.
Looking, thinking, touching, feeling, why you know?
Looking, thinking, touching, feeling, I know it
Looking, thinking, touching, feeling, understand?
mini mini all right Are you ready?
唯一無二のジョーカー手にするために
In order to obtain the one and only joker,
欲望さらけ出してる応答
they bare their desires in response.
離れてく世界のロジックを
As we drift from the logic of this world,
君は楽しめるかな
will you be able to enjoy it?
重要なキーは
The crucial key is...
すべてシークレット
all a secret!
後戻りは出来ないステージへ
Onto a stage where there's no turning back!
フラついているでしょ ここにいる意味さえも
You're wavering, aren't you? Even about why you're here.
切札はそれぞれ 互いの手札に
Our trump cards are each held in each other's hands.
頭と心で暴き出して
Uncover them with your mind and heart,
胸を撃ち抜いて
and shoot right through the chest!
自覚無いでしょ ねぇ 思い通りに
You're not even aware, are you? Just as planned,
君は動かされているの
you're being puppeted along.
単純じゃないの 駆け引きのヒントを
It's not that simple; gather every single hint
すべて拾って
from this psychological game!
唯一無二のジョーカー手にする事で
By getting your hands on the one and only joker,
理解できた愛のカタチも
even the shape of love you came to understand...
何処かの誰かに仕組まれていたの？
Was it all orchestrated by someone out there?
最後に笑う君と
Together with you, who will smile in the end,
加速してく 二人の鼓動
our two heartbeats accelerate!
神秘線は次のステージへ
The mystic line leads on to the next stage!
Oh... Yeah!
La la la...
ござる ござれ 何でもござれと
Gozaru, gozare, bring on whatever you've got!
切り捨て御免の マジカルワールド
A magical world where no mercy is spared!
I-N-G! I-N-G! 魔法の呪文 I-N-G!
I-N-G! I-N-G! The magic spell is I-N-G!
マジカルござる レッツゴー！
Magical Gozaru, let's go!
朝目が覚めたら 遅刻寸前
When I woke up this morning, I was almost late!
お気に入りのわらじを履いたなら
Once I slip on my favorite straw sandals,
駆け抜ける Avenue
I dash through the avenue!
抜刀 ジャキーン ジャキーン This is magical wand
Draw sword! Shing, shing! This is my magical wand!
どこから見ても 魔法少女なり
No matter how you look at me, I'm a magical girl!
ひれ伏せ 物の怪
Bow down, you monsters!
怯える悪代官たち
The corrupt magistrates tremble in fear!
ちょっと手強い だいぶ可愛い
A little tough, and quite adorable!
拙者のワンドの錆になるでござる
You shall become rust upon my wand, de gozaru!
マジカル居合斬り！
Magical Iai Slash!
ござる ござれ 討ち入りでござる
Gozaru, gozare, it's a raid, de gozaru!
マジカルな峰打ちをお見舞いするでござる
I'll treat you to a magical back-of-the-blade strike!
ござるプリンセス ござる ござれ この世界を守る
Gozaru Princess, gozaru, gozare, protecting this world!
完璧に可憐な姿をご覧あれ
Behold my perfectly charming figure!
魔法少女マジカルござる
Magical Girl, Magical Gozaru!
フリフリヒラヒラ そよ風に舞う
Frilly and fluttering, dancing in the gentle breeze,
袴の裾を ちょんと摘んで 決めポーズ
pinching the hem of my hakama for a finishing pose!
崇めよ 物の怪
Worship me, you monsters!
ござるランドの麗しきお姫様
The lovely princess of Gozaru Land!
あなどれない 凄まじい
Not to be underestimated, simply formidable!
秘密結社の上意討ちでござる
It's an official execution of the secret society!
ござる ござれ 闇討ちでござる
Gozaru, gozare, it's a sneak attack, de gozaru!
魔法少女は油断大敵でござる
For a magical girl, negligence is the greatest enemy!
ござるプリンセス ござる ござれ 魔法の国から
Gozaru Princess, gozaru, gozare, from magical lands,
お忍びで舞い降りた 謎の転校生
a mysterious transfer student descended incognito!
魔法少女マジカルござる
Magical Girl, Magical Gozaru!
そんな風に素敵を作りたい
That's how I want to bring wonderful things to life!
いつだって 可愛く
Always staying cute...
在りたいと願う
Wishing to stay cute,
忘れちゃいけない魔法 守りたいでござる
I want to protect this unforgettable magic, gozaru!
ござる ござれ
Gozaru, gozare!
いつまでもござる
Forever gozaru!
胸キュンな一撃をお見舞いするでござる
I'll strike you with a heart-throbbing blow, gozaru!
ござるプリンセス
Gozaru Princess!
ござる ござれ
Gozaru, gozare!
この世界を守る
Protecting this world,
完璧に可憐な姿ご覧あれ
behold my utterly lovely form!
魔法少女 まじかる☆ござる
Magical Girl, Magical☆Gozaru!
I-M-P!
魔法の呪文 I-M-P!
The magic spell, I-M-P!
まじかる☆ござる
Magical☆Gozaru!
Let's go!
ビビデバ
[Song: Bibbidiba]
つまらないデイズ もう散々ね
Boring days, I've had enough of them!
奇跡願っているだけの人生
A life spent merely wishing for miracles.
Watch me do...
呪術 秘中 トリック無しのマジック
Sorcery, in secret, magic with no tricks.
I wanna be free! だってまだ振り出し
I wanna be free! Since I'm still at square one,
The party ain't started
Hey タクシー ちょっと宇宙まで
Hey taxi, take me to space!
秒針は音を立てて
The second hand ticks loudly,
夜を急かす魔物のよう
like a monster rushing the night along.
人生は一瞬にして溶ける魔法
Life is magic that melts away in an instant.
それならば駆け抜けて 思い通り
If that's so, I'll sprint through just as I please!
おしゃまな馬車飛び乗って Drivin'
Jumping into a stylish carriage, drivin'!
あたしは大変身 メイクアップ！
I undergo a great transformation, make up!
我が儘に 燦めきに注意注意
Selfishly—watch out, watch out for the sparkle!
洒落た街で Dancin'
Dancin' in a stylish city!
左様なら グッバイ 劣等感
Farewell, goodbye, inferiority complex!
何時かは喝采 クラップ オーディエンス
Someday there'll be cheers, clap audience!
皆々 ご唱和あれ！
Everyone, chant along with me!
Bibbidi-Bobbidi-Boo-wah
Bibbidi-Bobbidi-Boo-wah Yeah
混んがらがっても仕様が無い
Even if tangled up, it can't be helped,
ガラスシューズで踊る Tonight
so dance in glass slippers tonight!
Bibbidi-Bobbidi-Boo-wah
Bibbidi-Bobbidi-Boo-wah Yeah
今夜に明日など無い
There's no tomorrow in tonight,
ならば自由に踊った者勝ちでしょう？
so whoever dances freely wins, right?
ダ・ダ・Dance! ラリラリホ
Da-da-dance! Lari-lari-ho!
どんな問題も解は一つ
For any problem, there's only one answer.
白紙も正解も間違いも愛す
Loving blank slates, right answers, and mistakes alike,
本当のあたしの理想
that is my true ideal.
なんだか世界は限界の気配がして
Somehow the world feels like it's at its limit,
ただただ安心じゃあ心配
and just feeling safe makes me worried.
今すぐ Jumpin' jumpin' out
Right now, jumpin' jumpin' out!
Chitty chitty bang bang, chitty bang bang
唯々諾々に危機感抱く日々に
Days of blindly complying give me a sense of crisis,
ぎりぎり爆発気味
barely keeping from exploding.
たった今 発散してしまおうか
Shall I just blow off some steam right now?
まだまだBB弾 巧みに乱射
Still skillfully firing BBs in all directions!
一発じゃあ撃ち足りないわ
A single shot just isn't enough.
ついに導き出した君にアンサー
I've finally derived the answer for you:
灰になるまで踊って居よう
let's keep dancing until we turn to ashes!
Bibbidi-Bobbidi-Boo-wah
Bibbidi-Bobbidi-Boo-wah Yeah
おしゃまな馬車飛び乗って Drivin'
Jumping into a stylish carriage, drivin'!
あたしは大変身 メイクアップ！
I undergo a great transformation, make up!
我が儘に 燦めきに注意注意
Selfishly—watch out, watch out for the sparkle!
洒落た街で Dancin'
Dancin' in a stylish city!
左様なら グッバイ 劣等感
Farewell, goodbye, inferiority complex!
何時かは喝采 クラップ オーディエンス
Someday there'll be cheers, clap audience!
皆々 ご唱和あれ！
Everyone, chant along with me!
Bibbidi-Bobbidi-Boo-wah
Bibbidi-Bobbidi-Boo-wah Yeah
混んがらがっても仕様が無い
Even if tangled up, it can't be helped,
ガラスシューズで踊る Tonight
so dance in glass slippers tonight!
Bibbidi-Bobbidi-Boo-wah
Bibbidi-Bobbidi-Boo-wah Yeah
今夜に明日など無い
There's no tomorrow in tonight,
ならば自由に踊った者勝ちでしょう？
so whoever dances freely wins, right?
召喚ショーケース ～異世界転移した先でフェネックが悪魔の象徴!? 冒険から追放されたので、歌とダンスで世界を変えます!～
[Summoning Showcase: Reincarnated in Another World Where Fennecs Are a Symbol of Demons?! Banished from Adventuring, I'll Change the World with Song and Dance!~]
ハッ！ここはどこ？私はポルカ…
Huh?! Where is this? I'm Polka...
車にはねられて…気がついたら知らない人たちに囲まれてる？！
I was hit by a car... and when I woke up, I'm surrounded by strangers?!
これっていわゆる異世界転移！？
Is this what they call an isekai reincarnation?!
なんでこっちに剣を向けてるんですか？！
Why are you pointing swords at me?!
何が何だか大ピンチ！
I have no idea what's going on, but I'm in big trouble!
とりあえず にっげろ～！
For now, run away!
よっしゃいくぞー！
Alright, let's go!
冒険の刑 No way
Punishment of adventuring, no way!
どうすれば？
What should we do?
歌って踊れば
If you sing and dance,
きっと大丈夫
it'll surely be alright!
さあ ツメの鋭いキミも
Come on, you with the sharp claws,
キバのすごいキミも
and you with the fierce fangs,
Raise your hands
アガっちゃえ
Get pumped up!
召喚ショーケース Yeah!
Summoning Showcase, yeah!
カワイイは
"Cute" is
この世界でも共通のラブ＆ピース
love & peace shared even in this world!
剣と魔法じゃ作れない未来
A future that swords and magic can't create—
今 作れそうな気がした
right now, it feels like we can make it!
怖い顔してないで
Don't make such scary faces!
はい にっこり
Now, give us a big smile!
召喚ショーケース！
Summon Showcase!
魔王と仲良くなった尾丸ポルカは
Omaru Polka, who befriended the Demon Lord,
平和条約を結ぶことに成功しました
successfully formed a peace treaty.
剣も魔法も使うことはありませんでしたが
Though she used neither sword nor magic,
世界に平和をもたらした彼女は
she, who brought peace to the world,
勇者だったのかもしれません
might have truly been a hero.
ハッピーギラファーー！！
Happy Giraffa--!!
ねねちのギラギラファンミーティングへようこそ！
Welcome to Nenechi's Giragira Fan Meeting!
さあ！ツノとアゴをなが～～く伸ばして
Come on! Stretch those horns and jaws waaaay out,
おもいっきり、楽しんじゃおうね！
and let's have tons of fun!
それじゃあ、いっくよ～～！
All right, here we gooo!
アミーゴ！カケーロ！ビバ！ギラファ！
¡Amigo! ¡Caqueiro! ¡Viva! ¡Giraffa!
Kabu-Kuwa (Hey!!)
ギラギラ最高だね Kabu-Kuwa
Dazzling bright, the absolute best, Kabu-Kuwa!
Amore Kabu-Kuwa Yeah!
Kabu-Kuwa (Hey!!)
クリクリお目目ラブ Kabu-Kuwa
Big round adorable eyes, full of love, Kabu-Kuwa!
Asore Kabu-Kuwa Yeah!
愛の(Fu!!) ダンスはムーチョムーチョ(ムーチョ)
The dance of love (Fu!!) is mucho mucho (mucho)!
飛んで(Fu!!) シュビドゥバメロメロ(メロメロ)
Take flight (Fu!!), shoo-be-doo-ba head over heels (head over heels)!
みんな(Fu!!) 集まれゾロゾロ(ゾロゾロ)
Everyone (Fu!!), gather 'round in droves (in droves)!
こん^^Chu☆(Chu☆) Chu☆(Chu☆)
Kon^^ Chu☆ (Chu☆) Chu☆ (Chu☆)
パヤパヤ(パヤパ!) パヤパヤ(パヤパ!)
Pa-ya-pa-ya (Pa-ya-pa!) Pa-ya-pa-ya (Pa-ya-pa!)
すごぉい！みんなのおかげで、こぉんなにたくさんのカブクワたちが集まってくれたよぉ～～！！
Amazing! Thanks to everyone, so many beetles have gathered here~~!!
自分に拍手～！そして、自然に拍手～～～～！
A round of applause for yourselves! And applause for nature too~~~~!
ギラファギラファ ギラファギラファ
Giraffa, giraffa! Giraffa, giraffa!
強くてカッコイイ(E!!)
Strong and so very cool (E!!)
ギラギラファンタスティックなノコギリは
The dazzlingly bright, fantastic saw-toothed jaws
宝物だよ
are our precious treasure!
アミーゴ！カケーロ！ビバ！ギラファ！
¡Amigo! ¡Caqueiro! ¡Viva! ¡Giraffa!
Kabu-Kuwa
Kabu-Kuwa (Hey!!)
こん^^Chu☆(Chu☆) Chu☆(Chu☆)
Kon^^ Chu☆ (Chu☆) Chu☆ (Chu☆)
パヤパヤ(パヤパ!) パヤパヤ(パヤパ!)
Pa-ya-pa-ya (Pa-ya-pa!) Pa-ya-pa-ya (Pa-ya-pa!)
っと！じゃあ、これから一緒にスペシャルなトレーニングやっちゃおっかな～～？？
Right! Now then, shall we jump into a special workout together~~??
足を肩幅に開いて、手を前にして、
Feet shoulder-width apart, hands out front,
芝刈りパンプアップ、はっじめっるよー！
lawnmower pump-up, let's get started!
ブーン！バリバリバリバリバリバリバリバリバリバリバリバリ
Vroom! Bari-bari-bari-bari-bari-bari-bari-bari-bari-bari-bari-bari
ムキムキな Love me バキバキで Burning
Muscular Love me, shredded and burning!
「そう！」 燃えるカラダ
("That's it!") A burning body
ホラね 誰も彼も振り返るでしょ
Look, everyone will turn their heads to look!
ねぇ 見せつけてやろ
Hey, let's show it all off!
腰にはヴィーナスえくぼ
Venus dimples right on the lower back!
やれんのか Muscle 止まらない Work Out
Can you take it, muscle? Unstoppable workout!
最強になりたいかァーッ！？ (Yeahーッ！)
Do you wanna become the strongest?! (Yeah!)
ムキムキになりたいかァーッ！？ (Yeahーッ！)
Do you wanna get totally ripped?! (Yeah!)
この世の全てを守り抜く 祝福が、欲しいかァーーッ！？ (Yeahーッ！)
Do you want the blessing that protects everything in this world?! (Yeah!)
やるしかないっしょ バリバリで Work Out
We've just gotta do it, tearing it up with this workout!
ノー筋肉！ノーライフ！ ノー筋肉！ノーライフ！
No muscle! No life! No muscle! No life!
脳筋べっぴんなヴィーナス
A brain-muscle gorgeous Venus!
ノー筋肉！ノーライフ！ ノー筋肉！ノーライフ！
No muscle! No life! No muscle! No life!
お隣さんもマッチョマッチョ
The person next to you is also macho, macho!
ノー筋肉！ノーライフ！ ノー筋肉！ノーライフ！
No muscle! No life! No muscle! No life!
やる気ホンキ大好き♡
Motivation, real passion, I love it all♡
ノー筋肉！ノーライフ！ ノー筋肉！ノーライフ！
No muscle! No life! No muscle! No life!
頑張るキミとマッチョマッチョ
Working hard together with you, macho, macho!
Yeah
マッチョ！
Macho!
がおってこ！がおってこ！ がおってこ！がおってこ！
Let's roar! Let's roar! Let's roar! Let's roar!
きみの“がお”が聴こえると その日もちょっとやさしくなる
Whenever I hear your "rawr," the day becomes a little gentler.
おすそわけしたくて 踊って踊って踊ってんだ
Wanting to share that feeling, we dance and dance and dance!
がおってこ！がおってこ！ ジャンプするなら今しかないし
Let's roar! Let's roar! If you're gonna jump, now's the only time!
がおってこ！がおってこ！
Let's roar! Let's roar!
高いトコ 目指しちゃおうよ Let's go!
Let's aim for higher ground, let's go!
がおってこ！がおってこ！
Let's roar! Let's roar!
小声でも Say! ちゃんと聴こえてる
Even in a whisper, say it! I hear you loud and clear!
がおってこ！がおってこ！
Let's roar! Let's roar!
じゃあ叫んだら未来に届く！？
So if we shout, will it reach the future?!
がおってこ！がおってこ！
Let's roar! Let's roar!
みんなでなら446dB
Together, we reach 446 dB!
がおってこ！がおってこ！
Let's roar! Let's roar!
ここがそう 私達の最高
Right here, this is our absolute best!
Rawr rawr!! Yeah!
言葉にするとまっすぐすぎて くすぐったい 胸の奥が
Putting it into words feels so direct, it tickles deep inside my chest.
だから「がおってこ！がおってこ！」
That's why: "Let's roar! Let's roar!"
「ありがとう」の代わりを
In place of saying "thank you,"
がおってこ！がおってこ！
Let's roar! Let's roar!
ここがそう 私達の最高
Right here, this is our absolute best!
リルビ リルビ リルビ リルビ
Lilvi, Lilvi, Lilvi, Lilvi
ねえドクター ヘイドクター メンテしてよドクター
Hey doctor, hey doctor, give me maintenance, doctor
またいつもの例のバグ
It's that usual bug once again
ハッピー アンラッキー 行き来するモード
In a mode that swings between happy and unlucky
組み立て ゼンマイ式のココロどこだ？
Where is my assembled wind-up heart?
チッチッチッチッチッチッ
Tick, tick, tick, tick, tick, tick, tick
リルビ リルビ リルビ リルビ
Lilvi, Lilvi, Lilvi, Lilvi
おっかしいね おっかしいね くだらないね yeah yeah
How strange, how weird, how foolish, yeah yeah
ワケないね ワケないね ハイスペックなんで
No doubt about it, since I'm high-spec
最先端のPON やらなきゃ損
Cutting-edge clumsiness, you lose if you don't do it
ドキドキが止まりそう ネジ巻いて
My racing heart feels like it's stopping, wind my spring
リルビ
Lilvi
なんていうかエブリデイ ネジ巻いて ネジ巻いてよ
How should I put it, everyday, wind my spring, wind it up
ちょっとだけね ちょちょ ちょっとだけね
Just a little bit, just a tiny bit
ピポパポ鳴らして 夢を製造(つくる)
Beeping and booping, manufacturing dreams
ちょっとだけね ちょっとだけね
Just a little bit, just a little bit
でもちょっとだけじゃ そのうち足んな波になるかも
But just a little bit might not be enough before long
リルビ リルビ リルビ リルビ リルビ リルビ リルビも
Lilvi, Lilvi, Lilvi, Lilvi, Lilvi, Lilvi, Lilvi too
チッチッチッチッチッチッ
Tick, tick, tick, tick, tick, tick, tick
リルビ リルビ リルビ リルビ
Lilvi, Lilvi, Lilvi, Lilvi
ねえドクター ドクター メンテしたの？ ドクター
Hey doctor, doctor, did you do the maintenance? Doctor
wow wow
てか分からん てか分からん わけ分からん la la la la la
I mean I don't get it, don't get it, makes no sense, la la la la la
次元の呪いなんて祓おう
Let's dispel the dimensional curse
なんだかおっかないね おっかないね とんでもないね yeah yeah
It's somehow scary, so scary, totally outrageous, yeah yeah
これはもうテクノだ テクノロジーだ
This is already techno, pure technology
三原則だってメモってるもん
I've even jotted down the Three Laws
分かったらその手ですぐ巻いて
If you understand, wind it up right now with your hand
リルビ
Lilvi
病んじゃっても笑って ネジ巻いて ネジ巻いてよ
Even if you feel down, smile, and wind my spring, wind it up
ちょっとだけね ちょちょ ちょっとだけね
Just a little bit, just a tiny bit
キミがミスっても笑わせてあげる
Even if you make a mistake, I'll make you laugh
ちょっとだけね ちょっとだけね
Just a little bit, just a little bit
ほらケラケラなんて ケラケラ アイデンティティ アップデートして
Look, giggling and laughing, update your identity
ドーモ アリガト ココロカラ
Thank you so much, from the bottom of my heart
リルビ リルビ
Lilvi, Lilvi
ピポパポ ピポパポピ
Pipo-papo, pipo-papo-pi
カラクリしやしゃんせ
Welcome to the clockwork mechanisms
起きて起きて 電気羊
Wake up, wake up, electric sheep
こちらに来やしゃんせ
Come over this way
その前にひとまず ネジ巻いて
But before that, first wind my spring
リルビ
Lilvi
なんていうかエブリデイ ネジ巻いて ネジ巻いてよ
How should I put it, everyday, wind my spring, wind it up
ちょっとだけね ちょちょ ちょっとだけね
Just a little bit, just a tiny bit
オーダーメイド「オーダーメイド」 夢を製造(つくる)
Made-to-order, "Made-to-order", manufacturing dreams
ちょっとだけね ほんのちょっとだけね
Just a little bit, just a tiny little bit
もうバグでもなんでもいいけど 明日もちょっとだけ巻いて
Bugs or whatever, it's fine, but wind it a little tomorrow too
ちょっとだけね ちょっとだけね
Just a little bit, just a little bit
こんな毎日も悪くないよ
Everyday life like this isn't bad at all
ちょっとだけね ちょっとだけね
Just a little bit, just a little bit
でもちょっとだけじゃ...
But just a little bit might not be enough...
...そのうち足んな波になるかも
...before long.
リルビ リルビ リルビ リルビ リルビ リルビ リルビ リルビ リルビも
Lilvi, Lilvi, Lilvi, Lilvi, Lilvi, Lilvi, Lilvi, Lilvi, Lilvi too
チッチッチッチッチッチッ
Tick, tick, tick, tick, tick, tick, tick
リルビ リルビ リルビ リルビ
Lilvi, Lilvi, Lilvi, Lilvi
もう...
Jeez...
溺れたいな 愛ガチャぎゅっと はまる君の交差点
I want to drown, tightly hooked on love's gacha at your intersection
変わりたいな 気持ちもっと 言えよ ちょい危ないね
I want to change, express my feelings more, say it, it's a bit dangerous
ネオンの眩しい夜が 幾夜も過ぎ去って
Countless nights dazzling with neon have passed by
薄暗いドアの向こう側 零れ落ちた
On the other side of that dimly lit door, it spilled over
君の体温を探しては アルコールで塗り潰したフロア
Searching for your warmth on the dance floor smeared in alcohol
このデシベルが蒸発するように
So that these decibels may evaporate
気にしないでなんて言わないで
Don't tell me "never mind"
本当はいつも正直じゃないけど
Even though I'm never really honest with myself
気がついてよなんて言えなくて
I could never say "please notice me"
嘘ばっかり
Nothing but lies
Can't stop loving you
溺れたいな 愛ガチャぎゅっと はまる君の交差点
I want to drown, tightly hooked on love's gacha at your intersection
変わりたいな 気持ちもっと ブルー 飲み干すから
I want to change, these feelings even more, I'll drink up the blue
止めたいな 会話がぎゅっと
I want to stop it, conversations tightly...
絡まり ギリの通過点
intertwining at a borderline crossing point.
変わりたいな 気持ちもっと
I want to change, my feelings turning more...
イエロー ちょい危ないね
yellow, a little dangerous, isn't it?
点滅と減滅の間 永遠と快楽の狭間
Between blinking and fading, between eternity and pleasure,
居場所なんてない夜更けの森
in the late-night forest with nowhere to belong,
ホワイトクロックすぐ塗りつぶし
immediately painting over the white clock,
今日も真っ赤に染めてどうした？
dyed bright red again today—what's wrong?
そんなに急がせんなよ こらこら
Don't rush me so much, hey now.
ぐるぐる巡って経っていく
Spinning around, time passes by,
くるくる行ったり来たり くだらない
going back and forth round and round, how pointless.
のらりくらり もういいんじゃないけど
Lazily idling by, not that it's okay, but...
言えない趣味と言い訳吐いて
Spitting out unspeakable hobbies and excuses,
耳の奥底で繰り返す
repeating deep inside my ears.
イヤホンで聴き飽きた曲が
The song I got tired of listening to on my earphones,
そのリピートを肯定するように
as if affirming its endless replay.
気にしないでなんて言わないで
Don't tell me not to worry,
本当はいつも正直じゃないけど
though truth be told, I'm never truly honest,
気がついてよなんて言えなくて
and I can't even say "Please notice me."
そればっかり
That's all it ever is.
溺れたいな 愛がぎゅっと
I want to drown, love tightly...
嵌まる君の交差点
fitting into your intersection.
変わりたいな 気持ちもっと
I want to change, my feelings turning more...
ブルー 飲み干す身体
blue, drinking it dry with my body.
認めたいな 会話がぎゅっと
I want to admit it, conversations tightly...
絡まり ギリの通過点
intertwining at a borderline crossing point.
変わりたいな 気持ちもっと
I want to change, my feelings turning more...
イエロー ちょい危ないね
yellow, a little dangerous, isn't it?
ダンシン マリン
Dancing Marine!
もっと マリン
More Marine!
愛して！
Love me!
そう ビューティフォー ワーオ ビューティフォー
So beautiful, wow, beautiful!
ムクロビーツ 死後のビーツ ムクロビーツ 死後のビーツ
Corpse beats, afterlife beats, corpse beats, afterlife beats!
そう ビューティフォー ワーオ ビューティフォー
So beautiful, wow, beautiful!
ムクロビーツ 死後のビーツ 叫べナヴィーツ ムクロでビーツ
Corpse beats, afterlife beats, shout it out, beats, with a corpse, beats!
死んじゃったらご執心 あの世でビーツ
Once you're dead, you're obsessed, beating in the next world!
でも存外楽しい 地獄でピースピースピース
But it's surprisingly fun, peace, peace, peace in hell!
もうクヨクヨしないで ほら高い高いあやしてあげる
Don't mope around anymore, look, I'll lift you high and soothe you!
切り替えていこう
Let's switch gears!
ダンスタチュチュ ムクロダンシン ダンシン チュチュチュ
Dance dance kiss kiss, corpse dancing dancing, kiss kiss kiss!
キスでチュチュチュ
Kissing, kiss, kiss, kiss!
でもベッドはチュチュチュ
But in bed, it's kiss, kiss, kiss!
ダンスタチュチュ フラダンシン ダンシン チュチュチュ
Dance dance kiss kiss, hula dancing dancing, kiss kiss kiss!
ビートに夢中
Obsessed with the beat!
甘酸っぱいチュチュチュ
Sweet and sour, kiss, kiss, kiss!
ルーバー パリラドゥーワチュ
Louver, parira doowah-chu!
ジェダバダ ユソロ
Jussedabada yusolo!
踊ろ 踊ろ死
Let's dance, dance to death!
君たちと踊る踊る 無限にハッピーハッピー エブリバディ
Dancing and dancing with you all, endlessly happy, happy, everybody!
それでいいんじゃない？
Isn't that just fine?
愛したいし誰からも愛されたいのが
Wanting to love and wanting to be loved by anyone...
よくないの？
Is that bad?
いけないの？
Is that wrong?
ありあまる不死肌を許してね
Forgive my abundantly immortal skin!
契約
Contract!
わかったら返事！
Answer if you understand!
感動しました！泣けました！
I was touched! It made me cry!
地獄最高！
Hell is the greatest!
ムクロビーツ 死後のビーツ ムクロビーツ 死後のビーツ
Corpse beats, afterlife beats, corpse beats, afterlife beats!
あっちの草原で寂しいですか？
Are you lonely in that meadow over there?
ダーリンがいるでしょう？
You have your darling, right?
ムクロビーツ 死後のビーツ
Corpse beats, afterlife beats!
誰がククロビン アイアイアイ
Who killed Cock Robin? Aye, aye, aye!
待って どうせこの世なんて
Wait, after all, this world is just...
え 待って 港の一つ
Huh, wait, just one of many ports.
ね 待って 通り過ぎてくだけなの？
Hey, wait, are you just passing through?
ねぇ待ってって言ってんでしょ！
Hey, I told you to wait!
いたってノリノリ
Extremely high spirits!
キュートが昂じてヘラったマリンの
Cute went overboard and Marine went crazy,
根拠なく無敵なたぎらすボディを
with an inexplicably invincible, boiling body,
ごっそり蘇生中
completely reviving!
なんて正義の集中
What a concentration of justice!
荒潮神みたいに窓を叩くから帰らないでオールデイ
Banging on the window like a raging sea god, so don't go home all day!
断然ホットな夢中中
Definitely hot and head over heels,
ハートビートは揺れるチュ
the heartbeat sways, chu!
超はかなり超？
Is "super" really super?
ちゅ喋ればよーそろ
Talking in an instant, yosoro!
ビューティフォー ビューティフォーデイ
Beautiful, beautiful day!
美しく笑おう 笑おう
Let's laugh beautifully, laugh!
えい ハグしてギューってして 誇ってバーンダイ
Yay, give a hug, squeeze tight, and proudly burn-die!
みんな好き好き 何もかも手に入れたいです
I love everyone, I want to get everything in my hands!
ガチナチュラルでボッキュンボン
Truly naturally curvy and busty,
ごめん美女で今死んでも治りませーん
sorry for being a beauty, dying now won't cure it!
どんの荒らし かんの荒らし
Storm of don, storm of kan,
ケラケラケラ 逃げ出す
cackling, escaping!
どんの荒らし かんの荒らし
Storm of don, storm of kan,
地獄謳歌？
Enjoying hell?
どんの荒らし
Storm of don,
ぎゅだぎゅだぎゅだ 逃げ出す
sloppy, sloppy, sloppy, escaping!
ケラケラケラ
Cackling!
ラタタリホー 月と踊れや踊れ
Ratatari-hoh! Dance, dance with the moon!
ラタタ リホー 立って歌えば風が吹く
Ratata ri-hoh! Stand and sing, and the wind will blow!
ラタタリホー みんなまだまだあがるんだっタ
Ratatari-hoh! Everyone's still getting hyped up!
大波小波を掻き分けて 出航！
Push through the big waves and ripples, set sail!
アイ アイ マァム！
Aye, aye, ma'am!
ねぇ もっともっと チュッチュッチュッ 遊び散らかして ラタタリホー
Hey, more and more, kiss-kiss-kiss, play all around, ratatari-hoh!
アイ アイ マァム！
Aye, aye, ma'am!
裁けばそこが アンダー ザ ナンダーは 良い旅を！
Once judged, that is "under the whatchamacallit"—have a nice trip!
ららら...
La la la...
踊りましたらば 骸に花束を
If we have danced, bouquets to the skeletons!
踊ろ 踊ろ (ハイ！) キミたちと
Dance, dance (Hai!) with all of you!
踊ろ 踊ろ 無限にハッピーハッピー エビバデ
Dance, dance, infinitely happy-happy, everybody!
それでもいいんじゃない？ (いいんじゃない？)
Isn't that totally fine? (Totally fine!)
スキスキスキスキ 超愛してる
I like you, like you, love you, super love you!
それってよくないの？ いけないの？
Is that not good? Is it forbidden?
有り余るフシダラを 許して許して
Forgive, forgive our overflowing indiscretions!
骨々やドクロになっても
Even if we turn to bare bones and skulls,
終わんないカーニバル
it's an endless carnival!
楽しすぎて成仏しちゃいそう
I'm having so much fun I might just pass on to Nirvana!
ねぇ 反省しちゃうー？
Hey, should we reflect on our sins?
キミたちいい？ 船長のこと呼び止めて！
Are you guys ready? Call out to stop Captain!
契約成立
Contract formed!
わかったら 返事ね！
If you understand, answer me!
はーい！というわけで、7曲連続でお送りしましたー！
All right! And so, we performed seven songs in a row!
ノルマみたいになってたでしょ！
It kind of felt like meeting a quota, right?!
軽くここまでをね、振り返ってみましょう！
Let's briefly look back on what we've done so far!
はーい！
Yay!
7曲ですよ、7曲！
Seven songs, guys, seven songs!
すごいよ！
That's amazing!
サスペクツ！
"Suspects"!
久しぶりに歌った！
We haven't sung that in forever!
これ風真とシロコで歌った
I sang that one before with Kazama and Shiroko.
でもこれいい曲だからね！楽しかった！
But it's such a great song! It was so much fun!
踊りもかっこよかったでしょ！
The dance was super cool too, right?!
そして、ねねの魔法少女マジカルござるじゃきーん！
And then, Nene's Magical Girl "Magical Gozaru Jyakiin"!
あれよかったわー！
That was so good!
はい、ポルカは「ビビデバ」をやりました！
Yes, and Polka performed "Bibbidiba"!
いいじゃん！よかった！
Awesome! It was so good!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
そしてメドレー！
And then the medley!
我らのね、オリ曲メドレーみたいな感じになってて
It was a medley of our original songs.
忙しかったけど楽しかった！
It was hectic, but so much fun!
最後バリバリなのもまずいよねー
That "baribari" at the very end was crazy too!
最後バリバリじゃないだろ！
It wasn't "baribari" at the end!
あ、最後ガオ、ガオってことだよ！
Ah, I meant it went "Gao! Gao!" at the end!
そうだよ！がおーって言っただろ、お前！
Right! You yelled "Gao-!", you dummy!
もうさっきの記憶なくなってるやん！
You've already lost your memory from just a moment ago!
間違えちゃった！はい、で、そのあとが？
I made a mistake! Okay, and what came after that?
はい、LiVE DiVEですね！
Yes, it was "LiVE DiVE"!
よかったよー！熱かった！
That was great! It was so hype!
そしてわたくし、Intersection、AZKiちゃんの曲ですけど
And then me with "Intersection", AZKi-chan's song,
AZKiちゃんの曲の中で一番好きかも
which might be my absolute favorite among AZKi-chan's songs.
名曲！名曲！最高や！
Masterpiece! Masterpiece! The absolute best!
そして最後がマガマガで！
And lastly, with MagaMaga—
「スキスキDieスキ超Ayeシテル」
"Suki Suki Die Suki Choo Aishiteru"!
ちょっと難しかったねー！
That was pretty difficult!
よかった！可愛かった！
It was great! So cute!
船長って歌が上手なんだなってすごい思いました
It really made me realize just how amazingly Senchou sings.
改めて先輩たちへのね、尊敬が生まれました
Once again, it renewed our deep respect for our seniors.
リスペクト！歌わせていただいてありがとうございます！
Respect! Thank you so much for letting us sing your songs!
はい！ということで、ここからは嬉しいお知らせとなります！
Yes! And so, from here we have an exciting announcement!
こちらをご覧ください！はい、ドーン！
Please take a look at this! Here we go, bam!
ねぽらぼアニバーサリーグッズ発売告知となります！
This is the announcement for NePoLaBo's anniversary merchandise release!
こちらイラストはですね、にもし先生に描いていただきましたー！
The illustration here was drawn by Nimoshi-sensei!
今回は「天体パレード」という大テーマがありまして
This time, under the overarching theme of "Celestial Parade,"
私たちねぽらぼは占星術師を小テーマに描いていただきました
we, NePoLaBo, were drawn with the sub-theme of astrologers.
かわいいね！なんかちょっとセクシーじゃない？
So cute! Aren't they a little sexy too?
それではですね、詳細を見ていきましょう！まずは、こちら！
Now then, let's look at the details! First up is this!
プレミアムアクリル色紙ですね！
The premium acrylic shikishi board!
こちらイラストがすごい綺麗に見えて、複製サインとかがついているので
The illustration looks gorgeous on it, and with replica autographs included,
これめちゃくちゃ箔押し綺麗ですよ！
the gold foil stamping looks super pretty!
そして、続いてはこちら！はい、ドーン！アクリルスタンドー！
And up next is this! Bam! Acrylic stands!
かわいい！
Cute!
エフェクトパーツ付きの豪華なアクリルスタンドとなっておりまして
These are luxurious acrylic stands featuring effect parts,
大きさは15cm程度を予想しております
and we estimate their size to be around 15 cm.
色紙とは異なる表情になっているので
They have different facial expressions than the shikishi board,
色んなところで楽しめます！
so you can enjoy them anywhere!
続いてはこちら！はい、缶バッジセットでございます！
Up next is this! Yes, the can badge set!
こちらもね、2つの表情が楽しめる缶バッジセットとなっております！
This is also a can badge set where you can enjoy both facial expressions!
そして続いてはこちら！鍵モチーフキーホルダー！
And next up is this! Key motif keychains!
こちらメインビジュアルで持っている杖をイメージした...
These are key motifs inspired by the wands in the main visual...
鍵モチーフキーホルダーとなっておりますー
These are our key-motif keychains!
それぞれメンバーカラーが異なる右上に小さなビジューがついてまーす
Each has a small jewel in our member color on the top right!
かわいい！ / おしゃれ！ / おしゃれ！欲しい！
Cute! / Stylish! / So stylish, I want it!
そして続いてはこちら！
And next up is this!
コレクションBOXでございます！
It's the Collection Box!
おー！ / 何これ何これ！ / すげー！
Ooh! / What's this, what's this?! / Awesome!
本型BOXに4人の鍵モチーフキーホルダーがセットになった
It's a book-shaped box set with all four of our key-motif keychains,
そんな感じになっております。表紙はもちろん
something like that. The front cover of course,
背表紙や裏表紙のデザインもこだわった満足感たっぷりのボックスでございます！
and the spine and back cover designs are detailed too, making it a very satisfying box!
いいね！ / 飾れる！飾れる！ / いい！
Nice! / You can display it! / Nice!
さて、そしてさらにですね、お知らせがあります！
Now, and we also have another announcement!
わー！ / 何でしょう何でしょう！
Yay! / What is it, what is it?
なんと、こちらです！
It is this!
おー！ / 何これ？！
Oh! / What's this?!
ねぽらぼの新曲！
Nepolabo's new song!
おー！ / わー！
Oh! / Yay!
『#めろぞーま』がこのあと24時、18時の...18日の0時からデジタルリリース！
"#Melozoma" will be digitally released right after this at 24:00, 0:00 on the 18th!
されまーす！ / イエーイ！
It's coming! / Yay!
めろぞーま一体何なんだ？ / 何だろうね、めろぞーま
What on earth is Melozoma? / I wonder what it is, Melozoma.
そしてこの後新曲を披露しますので
And we'll be performing this new song right after this,
絶対聴いてくださーい！ / はい！
so please be sure to listen to it! / Yes!
よろしく！ / めろぞーま勝とう！ / めろぞーまだねー
Please do! / Let's win with Melozoma! / Melozoma indeed.
そしてですね、我ら5期生周年ということで、各個人のチャンネルにてMVがアップされておりますので、ぜひチェックしてみてください！
Also, since it's our 5th Gen anniversary, MVs have been uploaded to each of our individual channels, so please check them out!
はーい！
Yes!
こちらラミィが『コズミック・ワンダフル・ツアー』をあげております！
For mine, Lamy released "Cosmic Wonderful Tour"!
はい！ねねは『ハイパージャンピン』！
Yes! Nene released "Hyper Jumpin'"!
ぼたんは『ひとつになる声』あげてます
Botan released "Hitotsu ni Naru Koe".
ポルカは『Twinkle 4 You』あげてます！
Polka released "Twinkle 4 You"!
見てくださーい！ / 見てね！ / 聴いてください
Please check them out! / Watch them! / Please listen!
じゃ個人の、お知らせ行こうか
Then, shall we move on to individual announcements?
はい、そうですね！えっとラミィが8月15日にて発売した
Yes! So, Lamy's 1st album released on August 15th,
おめでとう！ / おめでとうございます！
Congratulations! / Congrats!
ファーストアルバム『Fleur de neige』が予約受付中となっております！
"Fleur de neige", is currently available for pre-order!
おめでとうございます！
Congratulations!
ねねはオリ曲の『ごきげんドリンクバー』のMVが出ております！
For Nene, the MV for my original song "Gokigen Drink Bar" is out!
はい！あとソロライブのね、配信チケットまだ販売中なのでチェックよろしくです！
Yes! Also, stream tickets for my solo live are still on sale, so please check that out too!
よろしくー！
Please do!
ポルカです！ポルカは『燦然燃焼』のフルアニメーションMVが出ましたー！
Polka here! Polka's full animation MV for "Sanzen Nenshou" is out!
みんな一般見てねー！ / 見てねー！
Everyone, watch it a lot! / Watch it!
そして私はですね、個人周年グッズ発売中でございます。ぜひ手に入れてみてください。そして...
And as for me, my personal anniversary merch is currently on sale. Please be sure to get yours! And...
あの私、誕生日が9月なので、そろそろね、あの誕生日のね、お知らせも後々発表できると思いますので...
since my birthday is in September, I think I'll be able to make an announcement about my birthday soon as well...
ぜひTwitter、Xなり、私のチャンネルなりチェックしてみてくださーい！
So please check my Twitter/X or my channel!
はーい！
Okay!
というわけで！以上、ねぽらぼアニバーサリーグッズ情報とリリース情報でした！
And with that! That concludes the Nepolabo anniversary merch and release information!
ありがとうございまーす！ / よろしくね！
Thank you so much! / Looking forward to it!
はい、というわけでいよいよライブもクライマックス！ / イエーイ！
Alright, so the live is finally reaching its climax! / Yay!
ラストはさっきの新曲を踊って歌ってやりたいと思いまーす！
For the finale, we'd like to sing and dance to our new song from earlier!
イエーイ！
Yay!
みんなメロゾーマになる気持ちあったかー？ / あったかー / メロゾーマか
Is everyone ready in their hearts to become Melozoma? / Ready! / Melozoma, huh.
はい！めろぞーま、みんなコメントの準備もちょっと、してほしいな！めろぞーまなんで、
Yes! Melozoma, we'd love for everyone to get ready in the comments too! It's Melozoma,
覚えてください！ / 打ってね！ / コメント書いてください！
so remember it! / Type it out! / Please leave a comment!
そしてラストは魔道ゴンドラに乗って歌いまーす！
And at the end, we'll ride the Magic Gondola and sing!
お！何だ魔道ゴンドラって！
Oh! What's a Magic Gondola?!
みんな準備いいですかー？ / 準備しなきゃ！ / はいはい！
Is everyone ready? / We gotta get ready! / Yes, yes!
みんなメロゾーマ準備してー！ / めろぞーま！ / めろぞーま！
Everyone, get your Melozoma ready! / Melozoma! / Melozoma!
ということで、じゃあこれはメロゾーマも、これ極大魔法か？ / そうだね！
So then, is this Melozoma ultimate magic too? / Seems so!
デカそうだね！ / デカそうだよね！ / でかでか魔法だよ！
Sounds huge! / It does sound huge! / It's super huge magic!
上からゴンドラが降りてくるので、みんなで一緒にめろぞーまって打って、こっちは喋るでいいか
The gondola will descend from above, so everyone type "Melozoma" together, and we can just say it out loud, right?
オッケー！ / オッケー！
Okay! / Okay!
じゃあ行くぞー！せーの！
Here we go! Ready, set...
めろぞーまー！
Melozoma-!
おおー！ / 来た！ / 来る？ / 来た来た来た！
Ooh! / It's here! / Is it coming? / Here it comes, here it comes!
うわー！ / おー、来ましたー！
Whoa! / Oh, it's here!
降りてきた！ / え、これ乗れる？ / 乗れますかね？ / 乗りますか！
It came down! / Eh, can we ride this? / Can we get on? / Let's get on!
慌てずに！ / はい！ / 着いてくださーい！ / はい！
Don't rush! / Yes! / Please step on! / Okay!
じゃあね、みなさん最後まで盛り上がっていきましょー！ / 盛り上がっていきましょー！
Alright then, everyone, let's keep the hype going until the very end! / Let's get hyped!
じゃあ曲名もう一回言っちゃう？ / 言っちゃう！
Shall we say the song title one more time? / Let's say it!
じゃあみんな聴いてくださーい！せーの！
Then everyone, please listen! Ready, set...
#めろぞーま！
"#Melozoma!"
とろけちゃって らびゅ ずっと ずっと
Melt away, I love you, forever and ever
頭の中 ハート いっぱいに なって
My head is completely filled with hearts
ほら もっと もっと
Look, more and more,
釘付けになれ #めろぞーまっ
become captivated by us, #Melozoma!
(ever lasting love me...)
(ever lasting love you...)
女の子は魔法使い
Girls are magical witches,
神様がくれた悪戯（プレゼント）
a playful gift from God.
恋しちゃったりだって 思わせぶりだって
Falling in love or playing hard to get,
必然的 outcome！
it's an inevitable outcome!
甘い 酸っぱい ほろ苦い カラフルなポーション使い分けて
Sweet, sour, bittersweet—mixing and matching colorful potions,
キミにかけたい呪文 囁くの
I whisper the spell I want to cast on you.
...なんて 恥ずかしい妄想が
...Such embarrassing delusions
胸の中を駆け巡る ギルティ！
race through my heart—so guilty!
だってそばにいてほしいから
Because I just want you by my side,
メロがる呪文...#めろぞーまっ
I cast the bewitching spell... #Melozoma!
とろけちゃって love you ずっとずっと
Melt away, love you forever and ever
頭の中ハートいっぱいになって
My head gets completely full of hearts
ほら もっともっと
Look, more and more
釘付けになれ めろぞーまっ
Be totally captivated, #Mellowzoma!
Ever lasting love me...
Ever lasting love you...
レディファーストってなんかいや
I don't really like "ladies first"
私ファーストが絶対です
"Me first" is an absolute must!
優しさもぬくもりも
Your kindness and your warmth,
時間も感情だって独占させて Fall in love
let me monopolize your time and feelings, fall in love
カラフルだけどトゲ張って
Colorful yet covered in prickles,
こんぺいとうみたいなこの純情を
like konpeito candy, this pure heart of mine
食べて欲しいな ほら、あーん、口あけて
I want you to eat it—come on, say "aah", open wide
…まただ、おかしな思考回路が
...Here it goes again, this crazy train of thought
自律神経バグらす ギルティ！
glitching out my nervous system, guilty!
こんな気持ちはじめてなんだもん…
Because this is the first time I've felt this way...
わけもわからずに めろぞーまっ
Without even understanding why, #Mellowzoma!
とろけちゃって love you ずっとずっと
Melt away, love you forever and ever
両目見つめ ハートいっぱいになって
Look into both eyes and fill right up with hearts
ほら もっともっと
Look, more and more
溺れてしまえ めろぞーまっ
Drown right in, #Mellowzoma!
この魔法が絶対解けないように…
So that this magic will never unravel...
呪いと同じ類かもしれないけど…
It might be something just like a curse, but...
キミといつまでもとろけていたいから…
Because I want to melt with you forever...
ありったけの魔力を込めて…
Pouring in every bit of magical power I have...
キミと出会った瞬間から始まった (このロマンスが)
Ever since the moment I met you, (this romance that began)
ソーダみたいに弾けるなんて辛いよ
hurts so much to pop away like soda fizz
(永遠になんて) 空想だけど願いたいの
("Forever" is) just a fantasy, but I still want to wish for it
そんな魔法があればいいのに…
If only such magic really existed...
切ないけど
It aches, but...
素直になりたい めろぞーまっ
I want to be true to my heart, #Mellowzoma!
唱えたいな love you ずっとずっと…
I want to chant it: love you forever and ever...
(こんなにもキミに、恋してるから。)
(Because I've fallen so deeply in love with you.)
離れたくない hug you もっともっと
I don't want to part, hug you more and more
想い愛したい めろぞーまっ
I want to cherish and love you, #Mellowzoma!
とろけちゃって love you ずっとずっと
Melt away, love you forever and ever
頭の中 ハート充満になって
My head becomes overflowing with hearts
ほら もっともっと
Look, more and more
釘付けになれ めろぞーまっ
Be totally captivated, #Mellowzoma!
解けないで とっておきの魔法
Don't ever break, my special magic
クラクラさせてやる メルティ
I'll make your head spin, melty!
いつまでも 私だけ見てて
Keep your eyes on only me forever
唱える めろぞーまっ
I chant it: #Mellowzoma!
解かないで とっておきの呪文
Don't ever dispel my special spell
ドキドキしてたいの メルシィ
I want my heart to keep racing, merci!
いつまでも 私を愛してね
Love me forever and always, okay?
唱える めろぞーまっ
I chant it: #Mellowzoma!
イチコロね めろぞーまっ
Totally head over heels, #Mellowzoma!